[dramatic music]
On May 10, 1940,
without a declaration of war,
Germany struck against
neutral Holland.
Paratroopers and panzers
overpowered
the Dutch peacetime army,
with its obsolete weapons.
In 15 minutes they started fires
which destroyed the city centre
and struck terror
into the population.
176,000 troops landed
in the first 24 hours.
Using Holland's excellent roads,
Hitler's columns raced
across the flat countryside before
the Allies could come to the rescue.
That night, as Rotterdam blazed,
the Dutch people were leaderless.
Germany imposed a new
administration
headed by a Reich commissioner
personally responsible to Hitler
and empowered to rule by decree.
Faced with the prospect
of Nazi rule,
more than 300 Dutchmen,
mainly Jews, preferred
to commit suicide.
Maybe they were the enemy to us,
but, really, true, they didn't
see us an enemy at that moment
at least, you see,
because we were just
hotel employees,
and so long as we didn't
bother them,
they accept everything, you see.
We were completely stunned,
and psychologically broken.
[David] When he died,
he had offices in Jermyn Street.
The snow leopard is an
almost mythical creature,
an icon of the wilderness,
an animal few humans have
ever glimpsed
for its world is one
we seldom visit.
[woman laughs]