I well remember your arrival
at Darlington Hall.
You came somewhat unexpectedly,
one might even say impulsively...
while we were dead in the middle
of the Charlgrove meet.
- Bad business. How are you managing?
- I've found two first-rate replacements.
Miss Kenton, a young woman
with excellent references.
Very pleasing demeanor.
Appears to be very able.
And a man with
considerable experience.
Older and happy
to be under-butler.
Name?
Stevens, sir.
Stevens?
Yes, sir.
That's your name.
He's my father, sir.
Really?
Couldn't do better.
I'd like to see him sometime.
Miss Kenton, you are of
very great value to this house.
I appreciate your kindness.
I prefer to keep things
as they are.
I'm not leaving. I have
nowhere to go. I have no family.
Yes, I am a coward.
I'm frightened of leaving,
that's all there is to it.
Now, come on.
Sit down, damn it!
It is wrong to dismiss my girls.
A sin as great as any sin
ever committed.
I look out at the world and see
nothing but loneliness,
and it frightens me.
- What about yourself, then, Sarah?
- Oh, I don't know.
That's a serious sort
of a name.
Will there be
anything else?
Not turning a hair, he goes
to the drawing room.