[dramatic music]
So you're sure
you'll be all right?
- What, Basil?
- You'll be all right?
Will you get me my bed jacket?
Bed jacket.
In the drawer, the blue one,
in the drawer!
Now, you won't forget
the fire drill tomorrow?
I won't, dear. I can
cope, you know.
This one?
That's not blue.
It's got blue things on it.
They're flowers,
and I didn't ask
for the one with flowers, did I?
No, you didn't.
I only picked that
one up to annoy you.
What?
You're only here three days,
you gonna play
charades every night?
This one?
- Is it blue?
- Bluish, I suppose.
And I forgot to scrape the mold
off the cheddar this
morning, so remind chef.
Right.
And try to find time
- To get the moosey's head up.
- Oh.
It's been sitting there
for two weeks, Basil.
I mean, I'm on my own,
the Germans are
arriving tomorrow...
You just lie there
with your feet up
and I'll carry you up
another hundredweight
of lime creams.
Still growing in,
still burrowing its
way down to the bone,
still macheteing its
way through the nerve?
Yes, it is a very
simple operation,
but it will be quite
painful afterwards.
Evening, Fawlty. Hampshire won.
My wife?
That's it.
They're taking it out
tomorrow morning.
Is she? Good.
Not her, the nail.
They won't have
operated till tomorrow.
- What?
- The nail.
They're taking it out tomorrow.
How did she get a nail in her?
You called, sir?
Last week. But not to worry.
¿Qué?
Look, go and get me a hammer.
¿Cómo?
"Hammer"... Oh, hammer sandwich!
My hamster?
No, not your hamster.
How can I knock a nail
in with your hamster?
Well, I could try,
no, it doesn't matter,
all right, I'll get
it, you come here,
and tidy. You know, tidy?
I get hhhammer and hhhit you
on the hhhead with it hhhard.
["Jealous Heart" by Al Morgan]
♪ Jealous heart
Oh, jealous heart ♪
♪ Stop beating ♪
♪ Can't you see the damage
You have done... ♪
[David] When he died,
he had offices in Jermyn Street.
[woman laughs]
and hope that your stay
will be a happy one.
Now, would you like to eat first
or would you like a drink
before the war?
Ning... That trespassers will be
tied up with piano wire.
Sorry, sorry, trouble
with the old leg.
Got a touch of
shrapnel in the war.
Korean! Korean
war! Sorry, Korean.
Thank you. We will eat now.
Didn't vote for it
myself quite honestly,
but now that we're in,
I'm determined to make it work,
so I'd like to welcome
you all to Britain.